Oh, hello.   ah
.  Nice to meet you.
Oh, suddenly,
a little while ago,
about 10 minutes ago, 20 minutes ago,
my phone broke, and now I'm
washing my hair and the
fan is on, so my hair is dry like this
.
I think it would be better to just say this.   My
head is a bit messed up.   ah
.   ah
.  Oh, my phone is broken and I only have
11% battery left, it
won't charge, the
charger is out, and the
internet
antenna seems to be broken.
hmm.
I think this crown should be set so that each person doesn't wear it.
In each YouTube setting.  So,
in my case, I thought everything would disappear if I deleted it last time, so I
deleted it, but it
didn't show up for me.   It's
showing up here, but
there's a chat window besides this one. As you
can see, the original text isn't showing
up here.
I think each of these should be gone.  I
was floating when I first started out.
Oh, yes.  No, my phone suddenly
broke down and I'm
feeling a bit frustrated.
I
need an alarm and stuff like that anyway, but I guess I'll have to set the alarm on my computer and it'll
probably turn off.  My phone battery is at 8% right now and the
antenna is broken so
I can't send pictures.   I
wanted to show you some photos, but it
seems like this isn't completely impossible.
Oh, my
antenna is broken.  It won't charge and the
speaker is broken.  No, how
can all this happen in one room?   It was
going well.
Oh, this is what I used to
use recently, I used a transparent case,
but
as I used it, it got exposed to a lot of sunlight and I
used it for a long time, so the plastic gradually started to
break.
So after I bought that case and
it broke, I got lazy and just
bought a new case and put it in.
If I had
put a case in, it wouldn't have turned out like this
.   The
wifi isn't working.
I didn't even apply for Wi-Fi, so even
if I wanted to use it at home, there's no Wi-Fi
.
Oh, my phone just turned off.  I
can't send the photo because I'm going out to the battery. Oh,
I guess I have to allow the Wi-Fi function separately there?  But anyway,
my phone is dead so I can't use the camera anymore
.   He
died.
How about
going to the service center tomorrow first
?
Oh, really.
Oh, I have to go to the store
in the morning anyway,
so I'm going to buy a new phone
. Oh, and I also fixed my car a few days ago.
The car's air conditioner is now broken, and it has
n't been working since the latter half of last year, when the heat was starting to subside.  So, I guess I
'll have to fix this before I start working again next year.  I was
thinking that I should fix this before starting work.
So this year, around April,
early April, I
went and the air conditioner said it wasn't
working, so it could be because the refrigerant was leaking, but
actually, once you fill it up, it'll
last for a few months.  This year, this year, I
will be able to use it.  Well, I
just
filled it out and came home after telling the story like this.  But
after a few days, it didn't come out again.
So I went back again.  Then, this time,
in the case of Porter,
there are 1-ton trucks like Porter and Bongo 3.
If one of their air conditioners
breaks down, like the compressor, they
have to fix everything else at once, which
costs about 700,000 to 800,000 won.
I went to Gongnara and they said it would cost 800,000 won,
so I went to a few other places
.  Then they all said the same thing
.
There's this guy who runs an orchard downstairs,
and the owner of the orchard said that he recently
fixed it, and he spent 700,000 won,
so he was
really worried about whether he should fix it or not, and he thought, "
Oh, the car is worth 3 million won, and it
shouldn't be worth 3 million won anymore. It's been a few years, so why would I spend 800,000 won on an air conditioner?" and he was worried about whether he should just live with it or fix it, and he
ended up fixing it anyway.
Anyway, I thought it would be difficult to work without air conditioning, and I
couldn't buy a new car because I felt it was a waste of money to buy an air conditioner, so I just thought I had to fix it
and fixed it, but it
seems like the same thing happened to my cell phone this time.
Oh, the supply plains cost 300,000 won.   I
guess I'll just buy the cheap A series for the price.
Ah,
first of all, check with the service center.
yes.  Oh, anyway, the cow just
arrived today.
Oh, I was going to tell you in advance, but
the person who said he would find out about Soul and such keeps
not contacting me,
and he keeps saying he would find out by a certain date, but it keeps getting
postponed and postponed,
and every time I call, it keeps getting postponed, and
he says he'll set a date and deliver it on that day,
but as
time goes by and we
get closer, it keeps getting postponed, and even on
the day itself, it keeps getting postponed, and
so on.  So I thought I should tell you when I actually get there
.  Actually,
that was until last week.
Oh, until yesterday, I was thinking that if I couldn't get a cow by yesterday, I should
just not raise cows this year and do something else
.
But the
cow that was supposed to be delivered yesterday was delayed by a day, so today he said he would really
deliver it, so I waited another day
.  So, if
Iso can't come this time,
then don't look into it anymore and just give
up on raising cattle this year. In a way, you can give up on
raising cattle for the time being and
just
do something else. Later,
when you can organize and prepare better and be a little more stable,
why bother doing this and that?  I was thinking that I should look into the land a bit more
and then
start farming and raising cattle again
.  But
after many twists and turns, the cow finally arrived today
.
But then again, this is
why I was really nervous when I received the cow
.  But this time, anyway, I
fixed all the iron siding, and
yes, I was
very careful, so there were actually no problems during that time
.  Well, it was the same last year and
the year before that, and
there were never any problems while taking classes.
Oh, that one this time.
What happened last month was a bit of a special case.
And one way or another, I was really
unlucky.
Well, it was unlucky that I flew to the Cheolchi Vice Principal's office, it was
unlucky that I came at night, and I
just
had a lot of trouble with all sorts of things.  I guess you
could say that my mistake was the biggest one
.  Anyway, because of that, I
had a lot of worries and concerns like, "What if this doesn't just go wrong once and keeps going wrong?" But this time, I
received it carefully, and just
like always, the cows arrived without any major problems, so I
received it well.  Of course,
right now they're tied to the vice principal with ropes,
so they're
tangled up among themselves and they're also wrapping themselves around the vice principal,
so we have to get it done as quickly as possible
before morning tomorrow and train them on the electric fence right away to
untie them.
yes.  Anyway, that's it.
Oh, but it's not over just because I received the cows.
I still feel
a bit uneasy because I think these cows are the
worst among all the cows I've bought so far
.   The
condition is not good, so bring it.
And that
little boy,
that little girl,
didn't tell me, but I
think he knew.  Or
maybe you knew.  There's something a little
strange about this.  It
was always like that when I bought cows from this person yesterday, and it was like that with other
people's
cows
too. This is my second time buying cows from this person this year, and the ones that ran away were also
bought from the same person for the second time.
And last year,
I bought
cows from another person. I've met three people who are small business owners, and
during that time, whenever I received cows from the fourth or fifth
time, or the four times
I received cows before that, I
always paid the deposit first and then
brought the cows from the site.
At the selling ranch, it was the
same today, so I
was thinking of paying the deposit first, but
instead of saying anything, they said they were sending them as small business
.  So I got it for now.
Well,
the condition of the one I received is not very good, so I
have two of them, but one of them is
very skinny.  He's so skinny,
I wonder how a cow can be so skinny. And he's so
skinny, and one of them is skinny, and the other
one is skinny, so his body
looks really healthy.  Well, the family is
also very clean and the fur is shiny
now. Usually, if the health is not
good, the fur condition is not very
good.  That other skinny one's fur is
also not that good.
But,
the condition of the fur and the vitality and
everything else looked healthy, but it
looked like it had a bit of mastitis, one side was
really big and the other side
looked normal.
hmm.  So now I
took a few pictures of that and sent them to the small relay person
.  After sending it,
I asked why it was like this, and they said that
even though it was a mismatch,
there was no problem with the somatic cell count and it
was a healthy cow that produced a lot of milk,
so they told me to raise it once and milk it well
.
Well, the other kid said it was okay too, but
then I said okay
and asked him to send me the account number, but
after we hung up, he said he
would send it right away, so I haven't sent him the account number since
.  I
don't know if it's because they feel a little bad about taking money or what.
hmm.  hmm.
Anyway, yes.  So
I think these cows might need some rest.  In the past,
I saw on YouTube content from other people
that those abandoned chickens
started to breed in places where they raise laying hens, and
after raising them for about a year, they
just sold them all for meat.
But there was someone who made content about buying
chickens that were destined to be sold for meat cheaply
and raising them
in his country home, free-range
.
But when I looked at his content, there was a part where he described the process of animals that had
lost all their fur and were in
bad condition when they first arrived, but now they are
growing new fur, getting healthier again,
laying eggs, and things like that.
It was as if some of those animals came here and needed some treatment.  Oh, I think one of them
will recover quickly if I just keep squeezing it well, but the other
one that's too skinny
seems to need to eat well and recuperate a bit.
yes.  So I just felt a little
disappointed.  I guess there is still some
lingering anxiety about this.  Anyway, I
finished my evening meal and came back to the first meeting.   I
arrived around one or two o'clock.  The cows
arrived around 2 o'clock, so I put them down and
spent some time with the kids, giving them some food.
Luckily, the skinny guy had a
really good appetite, even though he was so skinny
.   It would be
the worst if they were so skinny and didn't eat,
but they started eating grass as soon as they arrived
.  But these
factory-raised animals,
even if they are let out into the pasture, would take several days to eat the grass there,
but this one just started eating grass as soon as he got off the ground
.  So what is it?   If you
give them hay, they will eat it well.   He
ate well.  He drinks water well
and the other one is a little under the weather, but I
think it will take some time for him to adjust, but the dried anchovy fish
eats well and
so I
think if we feed him well and raise him in a clean and sanitary environment in the pasture
and let him get some sunlight,
things
will get better. That's what I'm thinking.
But the problem is that the
old man said things like, "I'm really good at it too, and there are a lot of bridges and such,"
but I actually thought that the old man was lying
because there was no black report card or anything like that
.  But even so,
if you say how much it will cost, it's not like
it's a scam, but rather
a lie, even if you lie, it
won't be a huge lie, right?  But
more than that, that skinny guy
didn't come out much, so
when he first started being nice tonight,  Yes, I'll have to wait a few days and see
.  I'm not sure what to do.
hmm.
Hello, Kwon In-ah and Kim Eun-kyung.
Nice to meet you.
Anyway, the cow is very skinny and
its fur is not in good condition,
so I am worried, but I
think it will get better if it lives well and recover
.  But the problem is,
it's the rainy season now.  It's already a heat wave,
so when it starts to rain, they
don't eat much, and so they
especially don't eat things like hay.  When it
rains too much, it gets wet
and when it rains all the time and everything
becomes like a mudflat, it's not easy to eat grass
and
when it's hot, it
doesn't eat well either. So, since it's a bit late in the season, I wonder
what will happen. It
would have been better if I had brought them here a bit earlier in April. I have many thoughts like that
and I have a lot of regrets.
Hello, Deungwoo, especially this year.
When boiling bones, is it okay to just use any apple cider
vinegar?
Would it be better to use vinegar?
Apple cider vinegar is a natural vinegar, right?   The
term natural vinegar is a bit ambiguous,
but anyway,
any kind of vinegar
will do.
Hello, Chokkai.  Nice to meet you, Sambidolgi
.  Hello Universe.
Oh, I just thought of something.  How about
using the weekend for something like a cafeteria camp
?  Participants pay a certain fee,
go to a farm,
eat the same food as the farmer, and sleep in pajamas
.
First of all, my house is a bit like a magic kingdom, but
I don't have a separate barn for the cows.
yes.  The cows just graze in the pasture
.
hmm.
well.  Camp
This is
what I am, but I don't know how to change the cost and do anything,
but anyway, I have to keep working on the weekends, and
now that the cows are here, I have to work without a single
day off on the weekends while I am with the cows
.
Well, I have to squeeze, divide,
and wash, and
things like that, so I
mean, Jackson, I can't really spend much time with the people who came, but
anyway, there are things that I can't fully concentrate on
.
Isn't there something about content that's worth getting paid for?
Hello, Nunupi.
Next year, next year, but
ah, actually, right now,
it's hard for me to say for sure what will happen next year, but
I think there's a good chance that farming won't be done next year.  It's not that they don't build it,
it's that they can't build it.
So, I
don't think it'll be easy to do something like that,
but anyway,
I'm not sure.
If I had researched the land a little in advance this year, I think I
might have been able to move in more smoothly, but it would
probably be a bit difficult.
yes.  Well, it doesn't seem easy to decide
to start again next year after finishing farming,
get permission to bring them in again in the spring, and put up a fence
.
So, next year, what about business partners? Well,
anyway, I don't want to do business with this guy
in the future
if possible
.
First of all, I won't erase the number, but I do
n't really feel like getting involved with you anymore.  Today, that's
the broker who bought the cow again
.
hmm.  How do you prepare meals when you are on sale
?  When I eat out, most of the time I have a
hard time eating carbs, and when I
eat with other people, I can only
eat carbohydrates.
Usually,
if I can choose what to eat,
I go for pork soup.   When I
go out to eat pork rice, I usually order something special like a
double portion or something like that
.   It's
just the most expensive, so I think it's the only food that
lets you eat that much meat for that price
.
Hello, Aedongari.
You mean gluconeogenesis biosynthesis?
Well, abilities may vary from person to person.
hmm.  well.
But I don't think there's anyone who can't live their life to the extent that they need to
.   There
may be some difference in your abilities in terms of total quantity
.
Maybe.  But
I think the ability to endure starvation while on a low-carb diet in a state of ketosis may vary from person to person.  Maybe.
I don't know much about this either, but I
think it might be possible, but if you're on a ketogenic
diet, a low-carb diet, or a no-
carb diet, and
you can't synthesize it to the point where you can't tolerate it, I do
n't think it's likely to happen unless there's some kind of genetic problem
.
I hardly ever get scaling.
I think my mother got food poisoning and gastroenteritis after eating raw persimmon.  My
mom has 8 months old Canivera and
3 weeks old Ryan.  In the beginning,
there were no particular problems with the symptoms of Ketoprol.  He
has never had any bowel or digestive problems in his life.
Since I'm on the Ryan diet, I only
ate meat and water, and it's
been a week since I started eating about 10g of sogwan per day.   I
suddenly
had a severe stomachache that I thought was appendicitis, so I went to the emergency room in the morning, but they
said it was food poisoning gastroenteritis.
I usually keep it frozen and eat it, but they said
it's okay to refrigerate it for up to 5 days, so I
put it in the fridge the day before to defrost it and ate it straight from the portion. It
kept getting cold, but I
ate the portion that was in the fridge on Thursday afternoon and got sick on Thursday night
.   I
threw up all night, fasted all day the next day, and
suffered from stomach pain.
The pain was so bad in the morning that I went to the emergency room.   I
only ate meat and raw intestines, so is it
true that the refrigerated intestines are the cause?   I
originally ate frozen fish, but
did I get a problem because I put it in the refrigerator?
It's been in the freezer for a long time and
it's a wooden tube and I can eat it, but
now he says he's afraid of the tube and can't
eat it.
We're on a diet together, but I've never seen you this sick in my life, so I'm
not sure.  I wonder if it's because of habit, but you only
eat 10g at a time.
So,
if you were in a situation where you would unconditionally become ill with just a little bit of food poisoning in a state where your stomach was too weak, then you
probably had a lot of related problems in the past, but you
said that wasn't the case at all, and that
Yoonble ate the same thing and
was fine, so it's not like anyone would
be seriously contaminated to the point where they would 100% get book poisoning unless they had a really strong stomach
. But I'm not sure.  I don't know.
There's only meat and beef.
If you said it was food poisoning,
did that mean it was caused by some kind of bacteria?
There is no need to worry about parasites in frozen stools.  I don't think this has anything to do with the parasite problem
.
Hello, Jubaragi and Gayeon.
But anyway, the amount you ate was too small
and the Yunblim was okay, so I don't know if it's because of the liver or if it's
just
food poisoning due to stomachache
.
Did you say it was enteritis?  If
it wasn't that teacher, then what kind of bacteria was
it?
Ah, I
don't know if it's vomiting, but there
were quite a few people who experienced extremely severe symptoms, usually dumping, as if their stomach was twisted.   There
were quite a few people who had a really bad stomachache and were rolling around wondering what to do, but then ate some chocolate and got better in 10 minutes, and so on. So, those people
often said things like, “Who would believe that Oksusan was dumping if they hadn’t experienced it?”
Are you feeling better now?
But anyway, I would like to recommend that you keep some
charcoal at home in case you have diarrhea or an upset stomach
.  It feels a bit like a constant state of affairs
.
Anyway, if you have charcoal, it's
really good,
so even
if you ate something toxic, like pesticides, if you pour some charcoal on it, it
will detoxify to some extent, so
if you have some charcoal and you feel like you have an upset stomach or diarrhea, try
taking it like this, even if it's a bit much.
There are many cases where it helps.
Bumping can of course be severe, but
when it comes to dumping, the
most certain thing to do is to try eating Okseol, but if you
eat Oksusan, those types of symptoms
stop almost immediately.  Yes, within an hour
.  Anyway,
if it was contaminated to the point where you could get serious food poisoning just by eating it, I wonder if other people would
have gotten sick too if they ate it
. I'm not sure.  Well, I think so.
Oh, of course, it's even more so when you eat food raw, and
even if it's not raw,
there's no such thing as 100% safe food, so of course, I'm not
saying this is impossible
.
But when you think about it in general terms,
the probability of getting sick from eating raw oysters, whether it's liver or meat, is
very low, so
of course, even
if it's oysters that are infected with the norovirus, some
people eat them and are fine, while others eat them and
do something about it,
so things like personal immunity or maybe your
stomach acid isn't working well,
etc. are important, but I'm
not sure.  But
since you said you never had that problem before, I
understand a little better.   The
trial results are scheduled for July 9th
.
yes.  It's a bit of a shame that the cow isn't very healthy
Can I eat 30g of Yangsaenggan per day like Sosaenggan?  yes.  You
can think of it similarly.
Hello, Youngjae.  I'm
thinking about eating raw meat every day because I don't feel like cooking in the morning, but this is my
first time eating raw meat every day, so I'm not sure if it'll be okay
.
hmm.
But I'm not sure
what you mean by not knowing exactly what would be good
.  So,
if you think of it as raw meat, it doesn't have much fat,
so it would be good to make sure you eat enough fat,
and everything else is the same.  Anyway,
grilled meat or raw meat, it's all the
same,
but anyway,
this is not
just eating raw meat every day. I don't know if those who ate only raw meat for meals
are continuing to do so,
but there are
quite a few people in that cafe who have been doing so for at least a few months
.  So, I'm
not sure about that.  If you have any questions about cooking, or
how to prepare it, or which part
was particularly tasty, or anything like that,
I think it would be a good idea to post a question in the cafe.
In my case, I don't think I've ever eaten raw meat every day
.   I
mean, I eat raw meat every day,
so I
don't think I've ever eaten raw meat for two days in a row, so
yeah,
I don't have that much experience.   The
thought that suddenly occurred to me was
that we weren't just people who ate raw meat every day
. We used to have a lot of potlucks with meat and stuff whenever we had gatherings or get-togethers.  It
was two years ago, the year before last.   Did
you bring some cows back the year
before last anyway
?
Was it after selling the cow?  Anyway, we
used to have a lot of hiking clubs.
Back then, we would get together and go hiking to places
like Bukhansan,
go up like this, come down,
have a potluck with everyone at the bottom, eat the food we had,
talk about what we had eaten, and then part ways. We
had a lot of gatherings like this.  At that time,
was that gentleman's shoulder fat?
Or
was it Ur's neck?  Anyway, you just brought
a piece of meat like this, about 1kg or
1.5kg, and you
brought tongs, right?
There were scissors.  He brought the raw meat whole, either with his bare hands
or with scissors, and
then he took it from there and
ate it right away.   I do
n't think you're here today,
but anyway, in my broadcast chat window, it was
really fun.
Oh, was it just you?
yes.  If you lift it with your hands like this and cut it with scissors and
eat it like this, it is a
fatty part like shoulder meat,
so there is no need to take out the fat separately
.
yes.  Yes, I asked like this
I think it's been over a month since the Oksusu dumping.  I saw a video about activated charcoal and thought it might be
because of the oxalic acid, so I started taking it today.
Will it help with oxalic acid as well?
Oh, my skin was itchy so I scratched it and it started bleeding.
It hurts so much when I turn my neck.   This
will now help prevent oxalic acid from being absorbed and excreted.  However, if
dumping the Oksusan is too difficult and the symptoms are severe, it is
better to just eat Oksa to slow down the process.
Don't just try to survive raw.   I'm
curious about what Demomagnetization products you use.  I have Mega Mag, and
then
there's Mega Mag from Trace Minerals, and
there's another product called Concentrace.  Since the ingredients of the two are slightly
different, I just mix them half and half and eat them.
I know that Kandeda is more aware of Oxysan, but does that mean that when Oxysan dumping
increases, Kandeda also becomes more aware of Oxysan?
That could be the case.
Does charcoal and bamboo shoots matter?
no.  It doesn't matter.  If you just
drink it as activated charcoal, you
can drink it as activated charcoal.
What if the cows aren't pastured?  It
seems like it would be better to eat it raw, but I
think it is especially good to eat internal organs like liver.   The
nutritional differences between types of intestines are much
more stark, and the differences in toxins
are also said to be significant.
And Korean beef is
not just a regular grain-based food, and
to create that level of marbling, you need to be deficient in vitamin A,
so
the purpose of eating vitamin A is also big.
When it comes to eating liver.  But there
may actually be less vitamin A than you think
.
And then you have to freeze it separately
and eat it, which is a hassle.
Why do the sides of my mouth keep splitting and my lips crack?
hmm.
well.
First of all, dryness is probably the biggest factor, but for
dryness, the
biggest factor is probably not being properly hydrated.  So, the
amount of water you drink is important,
but you also need to replenish your electrolytes.
If you just drink purified water, your
body won't be able to digest it this well anyway
.
yes.
I think it's important to take care of the proper amount of electrolytes, including salt, potassium, calcium, magnesium, and chloride.
Well, other than that.
I think there might be other issues,
but I'm not sure.
Hello, Minjurine.  How do you
eat when you have a fever or are sick from a cold or virus
?  I'm curious if you eat similarly to your usual
diet or if you add anything special
.
When I'm sick, I eat more liver and sometimes
take megadoses of vitamin D.
Other than that, there's nothing special.
I'm trying to eat more vitamins A and D.  The best way to get vitamin D is to eat a lot of liver and
go out and get some sunlight
.
But really, when you talk about earthing,
there are a lot of people who look at it negatively, saying things like, "That's ridiculous." But earthing is
n't something that only happens to people.
Even people who are negative about earthing in the first place have
had some really magical experiences that make you wonder if that makes sense.
I have had quite a few experiences like that, but
one of them was when I was just
in so much pain all day at night that my whole body
ached, I had terrible
chills, a really bad headache, and I could barely
sleep, barely holding on until the sun came up.
When the sun came up, I
really worked hard to see the rising sun, and I slowly
went outside and sat
on the grass with my bare feet watching the sun rise
.  And
after I started doing that kind of earthing, my
headache went away within 3 minutes and my body felt stable.
And then I went to the bathroom for about 30 minutes, maybe an hour, or
maybe not even an hour, and then I
came home and
couldn't sleep at all, but my body
hurt so much that I
slept really well for about five hours after that.  I slept.
It's like that, and I
have a cold and a runny nose, but the
moment I go outside and go for a walk, my feet
touch the bare ground like this, and the runny nose on the bare ground
is cool.
And if you put your shoes back on, the earthing
won't work anymore.  I have a runny nose again
.  If you put your feet back on the ground and
do the earthing again, the runny nose will
go away again.  But I'm not the only one who's experienced this.
When we have meetings
or
get-togethers, we often do things like earthing
.  But
when we gather like that and do earthing and such, he
said that it was a bit weird to just take his feet off and do it, so he didn't do earthing, but he doesn't really search for earthing that hard. He just does it when we say it's good, when I say it's good, when he
gets the chance, but in fact,
he doesn't really care about earthing, so he's
not the type of person who feels a placebo effect,
but he had the same experience as me: when he earthed, his runny nose stopped, and when he stopped earthing, his runny nose started again right away. The reason I'm telling you this is because
there's an American nutritionist named Christmas John who had the exact same experience.  That person
also had a cold and a runny nose,
so
he lived in New York and probably
went to Central Park.   I
went to Central Park and
did some fishing there.  Did you take a bottle of water and
sit on a bench or something?
Where did you sit?  So, while standing and
doing his work, he
would pour the water under his feet to
make them moist and then he would do the earthing
.  But was that place a bit dry
?  It wasn't like grass, so at
that time, it was a bit dry,
so if you pour water like this and
do earthing, your nose will
stop running and your nose will be clear, but
as time passes and the water
dries, it will block again.
Then, when you pour water again
and your feet
get moist again, your nose gets clear again.
I heard this story and
wondered if it really worked, so I
tried earthing when I had a runny nose. When I
actually earthed, my nose
went away as soon as I earthed it, and
when I finished earthing my feet, my
nose started to run again, so
I earthed it again and my nose went away again.
There are quite a few people in our community who have had the same experience.
So, if
you're sick because of something like that, I think the best thing to do is eat some liver,
take a megadose of vitamin D,
go outside, and get some sunlight
.  Of course, this is
not a panacea anymore, but
yes.
There are some really ambiguous aspects to this.   When we
talk about fish food, it happens all the time,
so I think there are a lot of people who
think of it as some kind of pseudo-similar angle
.  So, you're
saying that things like restaurants are okay, but what does that mean?
There are some people who think very negatively
of it, saying things like, "What are you talking about?" But it's not like I've
studied a lot about Earthing since I made the video, so I'm not
sure if any additional scientific facts or papers have been published about Earthing recently.
yes.  Anyway, when I was studying at the time,
this was ultimately the lightning that continued,
so
if I were to explain it in a simple way in a broad category,
I only knew it in a simple way
.  As we
continue to receive the premise from the sun,
the lightning strikes and it now goes
into the ground and recharges the earth,
and so the earth
is this huge mass of negative energy, and
we are now constantly connected to it and have to
continue to receive that negative energy,
but
due to various modern circumstances such as the Gomaunt Michang or non-traditional architecture, we are now
separated from the earthing or grounding that all animals living on this earth have always enjoyed, and we are
no longer able to benefit from it.
Oh, so that's how it is, it just has to be
connected to the ground.
As a result, those people are now
asserting principles and such things
.
But if you think about that alone, if you
think about only being connected to the ground, then
eventually you have to conduction,
so in a completely dry
place like a desert, earthing doesn't work, and it does
n't work well on a playground floor, and
things like that,
like Christmas John did
earlier, and when he was spraying water,
his nose was clear when the water was wet, but when the
water dried, he
said that his stuffy nose from the cold came back.  So, if you
look at it that way, on one hand, you might
think that if it's like that, then all that needs to be done is the ground and the ground connection, but what's really funny is
that it doesn't seem to be like that.   If
the child only needs to be grounded, then it
is fine. Since the
ground pins and
outlets in the house are all grounded,
these days, houses have
water pipes,
gas pipes, and other things buried in the ground, so
those are all grounded as well
.  If
I touch something like that or
connect a wire or something like
that to it and it
touches my body, it
becomes grounded.  It's
happening, it's happening.
But I think it's not just me, there are quite a
few people who
don't see much of an effect from that kind of earthing
.  That's why I
don't really do it these days.  But
it was the same in my previous house, and in the house before that,
when I lived on the first floor, I always
grounded it by putting a copper rod outside,
and then I wrapped a standard wire around it and
brought it in through a window or something like that,
and
when I was indoors at home, I would wrap it around my wrist or something like that
.  So
now that's grounded.
Of course,
if you just wrap it loosely like this, the folding
effect isn't as good as you might think.
If I hold on to it like this and try hard like this, it'll
be okay, but if not, it won't feel like it'll work out this well
.
When you actually measure it, there are some that don't fall that much
hmm.
But anyway, if you hold it, it
should be grounded, but in fact, as I mentioned earlier,
I had chills all over my body and a bad body ache, and I couldn't sleep at night, so I
went outside and earthed myself, and I
found light in 3 minutes. Even then, I had
connected this earthing bracelet to a water pipe and
the stand wire was wrapped around my wrist
.
But that
didn't have the same effect.
And after I finish eating, I sleep really well
.  I sleep so well.
There were quite a few people who had insomnia and slept like a log after using earthing, and
there were also quite a few people who didn't see much effect from that level of earthing, and if it
was just grounded and you could just accept the sound and
turn it off, you
should see the same effect with that, but
earthing products, or whatever, you
plug them into an outlet, so when you plug them into an outlet,
it's actually just coming in from the distribution line
or something like that, so let's say that's it
.  But that's not it. I think you should see the
same effect with just water pipes or something like that, but
that
's not the case.
So, isn't
there something additional to this that we don't fully understand yet
?
I think so.   I
think there is something to it.
But I think we still don't really know what it is
.
Usually, if you have a bad stomach, you are
advised to reduce fat intake, but if you have inflammation in your stomach, I am
curious to know if you need to be careful about a high-fat diet and what direction you should take your diet.  My parents
had high amylase levels, which they
said was an indicator of market health.
hmm.
I think it would be good to just stand there and take the supplements for a while while you eat.
In the end, no matter
what diet you have,
no matter what your
symptoms are, the
method of giving birth is the same
.  Unless it's a really special case, the
nutrients our body needs for recovery and treatment are already set,
so the food we can get those nutrients from is
all the same,
so if it's difficult to digest, I
think it would be good to get enough help from supplements from cows, and other than that, I'm not sure about the food.  There's
no particular reason to change it,
so if you don't eat high-fat, you
have to eat high-carb.  Anyway,
I guess I have to choose one.  Whether you eat high carbohydrates or
high fat, you need to produce enzymes in the same way
.
So, I'm not sure if this is
because I eat a lot of junk food for the longest time
.  I don't know.
Is there a way to test how much linureic acid is in the body?  yes.   We
do quite a few tests of this type now with red blood cells.
For example, testing the ratio of arachidonic acid to DHA, or
isolating body fat cells and testing their fatty acid composition,
may be the most reliable test, and
this will probably be considered a test as well.   I'm not
sure exactly how this can be done in regular hospitals, but it is
possible to do this test.
But I'm not sure if this is for research purposes or if
we can just go to the hospital and get a
checkup for general health management
.
But anyway, we can find out to some extent by
doing something like a fatty acid ratio test
.  Me in the end.
Well, it's Arachnoid, but
there are things like the ratio of DHA and things like that, and
there are a lot of things to look at, especially the ratio of how much omega-3 and omega-6 we have in the red blood cell membrane, so now we
can look at it through things like that.
Hello, Milk.  Do you
know anything about central sleep apnea
?  I
often eat processed foods including eggs and fish, so I
think I need to change my diet. Do you know anything about this?
I have a question.
Oh no.  I don't know much about the specific condition called central sleep apnea
.
But,
as I said earlier,
I think in the big picture, they're all similar
. Um,
[music]
chat has been pushed back a lot.
I'll read it quickly and come down.  I
borrowed quite a lot.  Oh, I talked about that fish
at length.  Actually, I
couldn't make today's broadcast long, so it's almost 11 o'clock.  I'm a little
late turning on the broadcast, and
since today is the first day, I'll only
do it until a little after 11 o'clock after bringing the cow, and
not for too long. I have to sleep anyway,
and I'll go out and sleep tomorrow morning, so
oh, this alarm alarm,
oh, it's frustrating.  Also, when I think about that broken phone, I have to
set an alarm on my computer and go to sleep.   If you do
n't turn off the computer and set an alarm, he'll
upload it for you.
Hehe.
If I have a candida overgrowth,
is it better to not eat liver raw?   Is there
a lot of sulfur in egg yolks?   You
said it's good to avoid yellow yolks, but does that
apply to egg yolks as well?
What about Berbeline for eliminating candida?   I
don't know how to get rid of conditioner.  Oh, this is
a little different from Hwang and Candida.  And I
didn't tell you not to eat sulfur.  That's why I'm telling you that when the sulfur-reducing bacteria
are in the process of eating, it
might be a good idea to reduce the amount of sulfur
.   The
nutrient called sulfur itself is one
of the essential nutrients that we must consume, and
unless sulfur-reducing bacteria are showing off, there is
absolutely no reason for us to reduce it.
Candida and the two have nothing to do with each other
.  If something is overeating and the
intestinal flora becomes unbalanced, I
think Candida may also be a factor
.  Well,
fundamentally, the two are somewhat different.
And
I
don't think it's related to not eating raw liver because it's said to have candida overgrowth.
What
happens is that stomach acid doesn't come out well and digestive enzymes don't come out well, so before I can digest it, things keep passing through to the large intestine in an undigested state, and in the small intestine, only half of the bacteria are given to this situation, and this causes overgrowth. In this case, it is
recommended that you take enough digestive enzyme supplements.  no see.
Candida
Market I think the most important thing is to know the root cause of why candida has become so severe and then
get rid of it.
Well, with all that removed, I'm
not sure how to improve Candida in its current state.  You could
try eating something disgusting like Sachromomyces boulardii or
something like that, which
could help.  Or, it
might be helpful to get help from an antibiotic.   If you've
tried everything else and it doesn't work, and you've
eliminated the cause and
adopted healthy eating habits, but the Candida
problem persists, then you
can try that method too.  But
basically, I think it would be better to treat the cause first
.  Now that I think about it, I
forgot about the glass of milk I poured earlier.
Would you like to taste some milk?
hmm.   It
doesn't taste bad, but it's a bit bland.
Isn't it?
Guys, this is the first day's milk, so we should wait a few
more days, right?
I bought raw honey and minerals, and I bought tres minerals, but
they are both in plastic containers.
Would it be better not to use it?  Or is
there really nothing to worry about?
I think Brita is made of plastic, but I'm curious to know when
plastic is okay and when it isn't
.  To some extent, this
is a matter of personal choice.
I think that if you use things like cans without washing them, there will be more microplastics in them.
But in that sense, for
something like Brita, unless you expose it to direct sunlight or something
like that, I keep
washing it anyway, so of
course, we use it after the initial washing is done
.
So I do
n't think there's much to worry about since you're not putting anything hot in it
.
This is why we end up consuming the largest amount of nanoplastics and microplastics from plastic water bottles,
because of the plastic pieces that remain inside the plastic water bottles during the manufacturing process.
So if you fill it with water once, wash it,
throw it away, and then fill it again,
those related problems are greatly reduced.
As far as I know.
yes.  But now that things like that
don't usually happen, and there's a possibility that it could be exposed during the distribution process,
that
seems to be the biggest problem, but now there are fewer of those kinds of
problems with Brita.
But since these guys have
n't done any tests, I don't know,
but I
think it's similar,
right?
yes.  I think there's probably quite a bit of plastic
.  I
don't think I'll wash it and store it.
yes.   You
mentioned that milk slurry is not good, but
does the same bad thing apply to coconut cream slurry?  Oh, I heard that the
corner cream product I'm eating is homogenized
.  The corner cream is also
uniform.  These days, it's
applied equally, so it
may not be in the same context, but anyway, the fatty acid
composition is a bit different and the
ingredients are a bit different.  But
in a similar context, it seems
like it might be bad enough,
because it's a little different from breaking down the milk fat globules inside the coconut
.  First of all,
milk is basically like blood without the red blood cells,
but
coconut is not like that.  So,
in that sense, it's a bit
different, but
in the end, it's about breaking down that region because it's homogeneous
.  That's it, that's what I'm
trying to do with the oil painting.
But coconuts anyway
have a lot of simple fatty acids and especially a lot of meso-fatty acids
.  But even though
these medieval fatty acids are saturated fats, they
are very easy to break down.  So,
MCT oil cannot be stored for a long time or
cooked at high temperatures.
Even though it is 100% saturated fat, it oxidizes
easily, so if you
leave it for a long time and then eat it, it tastes really bland
.  It's all cheap, so would
n't it be possible to promote those things a bit?   I
don't know.
Hello Jinni, Jayoung, and Gohan.
Hello Maeb, hello Maeb.
Nice to meet you.
How much liver do you eat in a week?  Oh,
I think I ate about 400g or 500g these days.
Beach surfing is really great.
I want to eat a few pieces of liver as a nutritional supplement, but I heard that liver contains a lot of pyrin
.  Should I be careful with the blood?
How many livers do you have at a time?  I
do eat a lot at a time.  Well, I guess.   Would
n't it be less than 100g?  You do
n't have to worry about 80g of lean raw fish.
I bought lamb ribs while buying lamb liver this time, but is that lamb shoulder meat?
This one also has a lot of oil.
What I want to ask is, my son, Soyi, who has stage 4 renal failure, said he
ate a lot of
GF and creatine when he had regular blood tests. I think it
was creatine.   The
results were much worse than before, so I
completely stopped eating meat and only
gave him egg yolks, butter, and a little bit of rice with almost no side dishes.
Does lamb have the same amount of protein as beef?
Lamb and beef are basically
the same if you eat the lean meat, not the fatty parts.  You can think of soy sauce and
saaggalbi as
being similar to shoulder meat
.  The bone on the shoulder side
was just cut off without being deboned.   You
shouldn't walk around in mud at home.  So, in the end, I think the most important thing is to connect with the Earth,
or on a larger scale, with nature,
without any artificial things created by humans
.
But if you buy mud at home, there are too many things between
the mud in your house and the
actual ground, so it
won't work.   I'm
having a Kanye Raise, how about a pot?   Would
the pod also be classified as dead?  no.
Potatoes are a different type of bean that has nothing to do with dead beans
.   When you
ask, "I'm eating canned rice, but what about the pod?", you're basically asking, "
Can I just eat the pod?"
I don't think it's really related to the issue of Kanye Rising.
If you keep eating that kind of candy rice and also eat red beans,
candy rice will
no longer be that kind of rice.  But I'm not saying that you
have to keep Kani Rice or anything like that
.  Anyway, your
pot is fine.  Well, there are
probably a lot of other things in there.
All types of beans are bad anyway.   It's
equally bad.  This is
not the case at all.  But,
as with all types of seeds, they do contain a lot of things like lectins, phytic acid, and
things like that
.  So, it is better to boil it,
boil it enough, discard the water, pressure
cook it, and eat it like this
.  If you eat it.
It would be better if you did it with your feet up.
Is the theory of neck pain true?  Our ancestors
ate soybeans and vegetables. Are soybeans the same thing?   I
support the fact that Director Gong lived well even though he ate vegetables and that the average life expectancy in Korea is long.  Korea doesn't have a long average lifespan, but
rather a long life expectancy.  The
reason life expectancy is so long is because we can provide life-prolonging treatment very
well.  So, in Korea,
there are many people who have a somewhat misguided illusion about life expectancy. I think they think that if life
expectancy is long, healthy life expectancy will also be long
.
But there are many more cases where it is completely unrelated
.  The reason why countries
like ours and Japan have long life expectancies is
largely because we have much easier access to the medical system.  The mortality rate of other oil paintings is
so low that it
has almost no effect on life expectancy,
but in addition,
just think about Chairman Lee Kun-hee
.   Has it
been over 10 years since he passed away?   He
passed away, but he didn't pass away.  That's why
life expectancy increases because it's possible
.  That's why life expectancy continues to fall in countries like the United States where that doesn't work
.  Rather, it
makes your health worse.  So, people's healthy
life expectancy continues to deteriorate
.  In general, the
incidence and prevalence of chronic diseases are
gradually
increasing.
hmm.  But in a country like ours, no
matter how sick you are, you can still go to the
hospital and avoid dying, so the life expectancy is high. But
in a country like the US, where it is difficult to just go to the hospital and avoid dying when sick, the
life expectancy continues to fall.
This is something that has a greater impact in a more fundamental sense than eating beans, vegetables, or
meat
.
And our ancestors were not
people who ate vegetables without any food
.  This is the same in any traditional group, and in
our country, when we eat someone else's food, we
go through various steps to neutralize it as much as possible.  Well,
after blanching it like this, you squeeze it out,
dry it, and after drying it,
you go through some cooking process again, and it's
all a rough
process of detoxification in its own way. And
in the past, you couldn't eat it 365 days a year like you can now
.
Even if we eat spinach, which is a food with that toxicity, it's unlikely that our country
ate that much spinach.
So
even if we did eat spinach,
we wouldn't eat it only at certain times of the year. It's not like we
grow it in a greenhouse like we do now and
eat it 360 days a year. It's not like
we store it in a cold storage and take it out and sell it when it's not season so we can eat it.
In the past,
there were no refrigerators, so
how long would we have kept vegetables
?  We just eat it in season, or we store it and eat it like
kimchi these days. When I
asked my father, he said that he would
just bury things like radishes in the ground and
take them out to eat. But
really, if you
bury things like radishes or radish in the ground,
how long do you think they will last?   It's
all rotten.
And if you're talking about things like soybeans, there are
almost no records of this in our country, but the consumption
in large countries like China or Japan is
not as high as you might think.  In cases like China, they
say they eat about 10g on average per day, and
in cases like Japan, they say they eat 30g
.  Traditionally,
I thought 30g or 10g was too much, but
now you're not thinking, "Why are you saying it's bad now when you used to
eat it like a staple food?
"
When it comes to grounding, the grounding effect itself
may not be that good.
The land is so dry now that it cannot be converted
.
Hello, Darebel.
Since I can't give my child meat during meals, I
give him a handful of things like Blue Star, watermelon, and cucumber with the skin removed to keep him from getting hungry, but not enough to fill him up
. This isn't a bad diet.  But just
because you fill your stomach with fiber
doesn't mean you won't be hungry.
So,
what is
this? I
don't know how much fruit they give you, but I don't think you'll feel hungry after eating a few pieces of fruit
.
[Music]
What would be a good milk substitute?  I
tried buying Visa Sanyangryuk, but I couldn't eat it anymore.   When you
say milk substitute,
do you mean something that replaces the nutrients of milk?
Or are you talking about a drink replacement
?  As for the drink substitute, I'm
not sure.
[Music]
If you want a drink substitute,
just drink water, right?
For that nutritional replacement, you can just eat meat
.   I guess I'll
have to take calcium separately
.  If you can't eat oatmeal, you
can't eat dairy products.
Medium carbohydrate, medium fat, I don't
think it matters.
Since it is cut
into small pieces during the processing, is it
okay to eat parts like tendons or membranes that are not chewed raw
?  Of course it is.
What do you think about expansion supplements like NM or PC Team?  Oh,
I think in most cases, they are sold at a higher price than usual.
yes.  Well, I don't know.
First of all, although we say it is anti-aging, in fact,
we do not have a clear definition of aging, and
NM is something
that David Clare
brought up, so it is
worth looking at in itself.  I have
n't really looked for data like this specifically for NM.
Just get your vitamin B3 from foods
.  This
[music]
Brita has a large filter size, so it
filters out some microplastics, but
not nanoplastics.  yes.
There is a separate filter for this Miss Plastic.
These filters that are commonly sold in our country
won't even
be able to filter out microplastics.   There
are many types of filters, and
now they say that
this one filters out 100% of microplastics
.  Although it is not advertised this way,
the size of the things that are filtered out by the filter itself is so small that
nanoplastics
can't be filtered out anyway, and
there is probably no filter that can filter out nanoplastics.
Yeah, yeah.
So, when checking that, I understand that they
don't just filter and check, but
use a different method
.  Anyway, it's
nano plastic, so it won't be filtered out anyway,
but there are filters that can filter out Miss Plastic, right?
But I don't think it contains that much isoflavone
.
What do you think about mountain depression?   The
original amulets didn't even have any acidity.   I
probably didn't have any mountain depression at all.
Actually, when I look at animals, I don't
think there are any animals that suffer from sanwoo depression other than those raised by humans.
So, in Dr. Press's
book,
if you look at what Eskimo mothers did, it
says that they slept with their husbands at night, gave birth alone in the middle of the night, and showed their husbands in the morning that their baby was born.
So, the process of giving birth was so easy,
and
I don't think I would have been depressed or anything like that while introducing the baby to my husband.  Ja.
What kind of log are you
talking about, a farming vlog?
It seems like it's going down pretty quickly now.   Even though I did
n't do much conditioning exercise while doing cannibalism, my body and energy levels have
increased significantly.
If I am not consuming the amount of protein I should be consuming on a daily basis, muscle
protein synthesis can occur sufficiently through diet alone, and this can increase my body weight
.
After 3 weeks of using the child's cannibalistic diet, the
pain in my finger joints disappeared.
There are a lot of people like this, right?   I
eat a lot of junk food, but does that
make me sick? Yes, yes.  It's not good to see.   Even
if you swallow the honey rice cake, if you
cut it into small pieces and swallow it, it's the same as chewing it and eating it
.
Hello, Nai.   I'm
not sure how much raw beef liver a cat should consume
.
Here, even the kombucha isn't a very good food
Oh no.  I
think kombucha is a good food, but now I
think it's better to just make it yourself.
So, since you can make it by removing things like caffeine and oxalic acid, if you
do it yourself,
then in my opinion,
kombucha is made from black tea
.  And in China, too,
people who have been drinking this kind of black tea for a long time do something called new tea. When we
say new tea, we
mean throwing away the water that was first brewed.  In the end,
to put it simply, in China, it's
like washing the car, so they
call it a new car because it feels like it's been washed,
but in my opinion, rather than actually washing the car to
get rid of the dust or anything like that,
when it's first used, the largest
amount of oxalic acid comes out, and the largest
amount of caffeine comes out.
So, I think the Chinese probably went through a tea washing process to enjoy the flavor of the tea as much as possible
while minimizing the toxicity of the tea leaves
.  And after doing these three teas,
we should also make kombucha. We
can consume the great variety of organic acids and other good things in kombucha while minimizing toxicity.
However, commercial kombucha doesn't seem to be made with these three teas
.
In that respect, it seems
like it might be a little bit less good, and
since we make it at home, it would be better to first
throw away all the water and then
make it with our own water
.
Now yes.  I need to sleep.  I'm
starting to get into cannibalism, and when I do that, I
get shoulder pain when I move my finger joints.
I think this is probably due to the dumping of Oksa.
Make sure to take plenty of vitamin K2 as well.
yes.  It's 11:18 now, so I'm going to
sleep and wake up tomorrow. I
'll have to train the kids in Jeonggyo Wolta right away and then let them out right away.
I don't think it's a good idea to tie it up with a rope like this at the peak, so we need to release it as quickly as possible
.
How about some solip tea and dog poop tea?
First of all, is mugwort tea different from regular mugwort
? Yes.  Mugwort
is a poison bomb.
Mugwort is
worse than spinach.  Yes, we
don't eat mugwort like spinach, of course
.  So, I think it would be better not to drink mugwort tea, and I
don't know much about Solip either.
Solip is
rich in vitamin K2 MK7 during the day.
MK4 is what our bodies really need more than MK7, so it
doesn't really matter anyway.  Of course, you
can eat MK7 and see more of the unique effects of MK7 and convert it into MK4 in your body, but there is
no need to eat it to that extent.  So, there is a
lot,
but if we simply say there is a lot, the
food with the most iron is iron powder,
right?
When consuming food, you
don't just eat it because of something in it, you
have to look at it as a whole.
I still think natto is bad because it's soy
.
yes.  Anyway, we'll try to broadcast again next week
I will make another announcement regarding the number of figures, but I am not
sure if I will be able to upload them this week
.  I will check the condition of the children
, and
then, after looking at the situation
, I will
again raise the issue of selling crude oil, crude oil, and crude oil rights
.
Oh, and I need to fix my phone too.  Oh, I
feel so frustrated.  Anyway, yes, see you next week
.  Please click the like button and
thank you for watching.
no see.